本作品之片源 字幕均来自互联网 仅供个人影视制作的学习 交流之用 版权归原电影公司所有
<格林>前情提要
Previously on Grimm...
河豚怪使人变僵尸
The Cracher-Mortel makes zombies.
我查不出为什么
I was not able to find out
你哥哥去了波特兰
why your brother went to Portland.
我知道 他带走了格林
I know why. He took the Grimm.
Eric逼我们动手
Eric's forced our hand.
是时候教训我那亲爱的哥哥了
It's time my dear brother was dealt with.
家族以外的人
Someone outside the family
怀上了皇室的后代
is carrying royal blood.
哎哟 你干嘛
What... Ow! What are you...
啊
Ah...
你得把已凋谢的花收集起来
You have to gather the dead flowers.
- Nick在哪里   - 他不在这
- Where's Nick?   - He not here.
我们觉得他可能逃过一劫
We think he may have survived the crash.
他可能被感染了 变了一个人
He might be infected. He may not be himself.
所以你得做好心理准备
So you need to prepare yourselves.
- 你能跟上他吗   - 我试试
- Can you follow him?   - I can try.
走
Go.
死而复生非意外 时间万物皆复苏
跟丢了吗
You lose him?
或许 大概 是吧
Sorta, kinda. Yeah.
这事没看上去那么容易 好吗
This is not as easy as it looks, you know?
这里除了Nick的气味还有很多别的味道
There's a lot more out here than just Nick.
而且我没法四肢着地
And I'm not getting on my hands and knees,
因为没法跑那么快
'cause I can't move that fast.
更别说这草这么脏
Not to mention the grass stains.
等等
Wait.
闻到他了
I got him.
- 怎么了   - 找到他了吗
- Yeah?   - You find him?
- 还没 但正在跟踪   - 你们在哪
- Not yet, but we're on him.   - Where are you?
酒吧向东大概一英里处
About a mile east of the bar.
Nikc跑得很快
Nick's moving fast.
好的 我们这就去找你们
All right, we're headed in your direction.
他们找到他了吗
Did they find him?
还没 但是很近了
Not yet. But they're getting close.
- Renard队长   - 怎么了
- Captain Renard.   - Yeah?
我检查了监控录像
I checked for surveillance,
但是系统好像无法运行
but the system appears to be down.
- 所以没查到任何东西   - 不像是我们需要的
- So you got nothing?   - Doesn't look like it.
好吧
All right.
那个 我要回局里了
Well, I'm headed back to my precinct.
有任何线索 给我打电话
You find anything, you call me.
我累了
I'm tired.
你能带他们上床睡觉吗
Can you get them to bed?
我想让你给我读个故事
I want you to read me a story.
- 好的   - 走吧
- Okay.   - Come on.
哎呀 我把吃的落车上了
You know what? I left the food in the car.
哦 咱们还是先带他俩上床睡觉 好么
Oh, let's just get them to bed, okay?
好吧
All right.
他在干嘛 John 快开门啊 John
What's he doing, John? John, get the door.
- 好的   - 快点
- Okay.   - Hurry.
- 妈妈 他好快啊   - John 快开门
- Mom, he's coming fast.   - John, get the door!
- 快开门啊 John   - 妈咪 怎么回事
- John, open the door!   - Mommy, what's happening?
- 带他们进去 John   - 带他们进屋
- Get them inside, John!   - Get them in the house!
妈咪
Mommy!
报警 报警
Call 911! Call 911!
先带孩子们上楼
Get the kids upstairs first.
快啊
Hurry!
带他们去我们房间 那有枪
Get them to our room! I have the gun in there!
翻译 小二 嗷牌烤炉 Sandy unicorn Kodi
■
校对 Emily 后期 总监 芒果干 压制 老鼠
第三季第二季
果然字幕组
快去卧室 那有枪
Get in the bedroom. I have the gun in there.
快走
Let's go!
帮我用书架堵住门
Help me get the bookcase in front of the door.
他是谁 他在这干嘛
Who is he? What's he doing here?
我不知道
I don't know.
带孩子们进衣柜 把门锁上
Take the kids into the closet and shut the door!
- 你要干嘛   - 我去拿枪
- What are you gonna do?   - I'm gonna get the gun.
嘘 进去
Shh, go in there.
- 嘘 别出声   - 爸爸
- Shh, just be quiet.   - Dad!
拜托 快啊
Come on! Come on!
妈妈 爸爸 爸
Mom! Dad! Daddy!
- 妈咪   - 嘘 嘘
- Mommy!   - Shh! Shh!
你们要非常安静 好吗
You have to be really quiet, okay?
- 嘘   - 妈咪 我好害怕
- Shh.   - Mommy, I'm scared.
抱歉 哥们
Sorry, man.
又跟丢了
I lost him again.
- 啊   - 妈妈
- Aah!   - Mom!
我想我们找到他了
I think we found him.
啊
Aah!
妈妈
Mom!
听着 别做任何会让你...
Now, look, don't do something that you're gonna...
- 我们得制止他   - 我就是在试着制止他啊
- We gotta stop him!   - That's what I'm trying to do!
妈妈
Mom!
爸爸
Dad!
爸
Daddy!
咱得把他弄出去
We gotta get him outta here.
矮马
Whoa!
没错
That's right!
就是我丢的 来抓我啊
I threw it. Come and get me!
你从后门出去 我引他从前门走
You go out the back. I'll lead him out the front.
好的
Okay.
计划废了
Plan's not working.
- 队长   - 抓到他了吗
- Captain.   - Have you got him?
算是吧
Sort of.
我在伯明翰路642号
I'm at 642 Birmingham road.
速来
Hurry!
- 现在呢   - 呃
- Now what?   - Uh...
我们怎么办
what are we gonna do?
什么 你要朝他开枪吗
What, are you gonna shoot him?
哎 除非咱能想办法困住他
Well, unless we can find a way to trap him,
要不然我就真得伤着他了
I'm gonna wound him.
我们没有多少时间了
We don't have much time.
利用这间放干草的阁楼怎么样
What about the hay loft?
我不知道  我是说 也许我们可以...
I don't know. I mean, maybe we could...
哇哦
Whoa!
嘿 Nick
Hey, Nick!
听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
听到我说话吗  知道我是谁吗
Can you hear me? Do you know who I am?
Nick 是我们啊 兄弟
Nick, it's us, man!
别冲动 别冲动 Nick
Don't do it. Don't do it, Nick!
他冲动了
He's doing it.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
你觉得我们把他弄死了吗
Do you think we killed him?
没有  咱们先把他围起来
We didn't. Let's close him in.
- Nick在哪儿   - 在里面  我们把他困住了
- Where's Nick?   - Inside. We have him trapped.
- 但是困不了多久   - 他受伤了吗
- Probably not for long.   - Is he hurt?
就算受伤了 我觉得他自己也不知道
If he is, I don't think he knows it.
Juliette 你要理解
Juliette, you have to understand,
Nick现在满是兽性 欠缺人性
Nick is more animal than man right now.
他在哪儿
Where is he?
先生 我们已经控制住局面了
Sir, we have the situation under control.
你们是警察吗  你们怎么来的这么快
You're cops? How did you get here so fast?
我刚才才报的警
I just called 911.
我们一直在追踪嫌疑人
We've been following the suspect.
我要你把枪放下 回到你家里去
I need you to put the gun down and go back in the house.
他刚刚想要杀了我和我的家人
He tried to kill me and my family.
- 有人受伤吗   - 没有
- Is anyone hurt?   - No.
但是他们快吓死了
But they're scared to death.
这家伙疯了  他是谁
This guy's insane. Who is he?
他叫 呃...
His name is, uh...
Thomas Schirach
Thomas Schirach.
先生 把枪给我 然后回家去吧
Sir, give me the gun and go back in the house.
我不会把枪给你  我会回去的
I'm not giving you my gun. I'll go back inside,
但我的妻子和孩子还在里面
but my wife and kids are in there.
要是这疯子再发疯 我...
And if this maniac gets out on the loose again, I...
好了 我们要进去了
All right, we're gonna go in.
离远点
Stay back...
主要保证备好解药
And just make sure that thing is ready.
来吧
Come on.
- 咱去抓住他   - 呃 不能空手抓啊
- Let's take him.   - Uh... Not like this.
我试过了
I tried.
能适应吗
You okay?
我希望我也能这样啊
I wish I could do that.
哦 Nick Nick
Oh! Nick! Nick!
Nick 别这样 我发誓
Nick, don't do it. I swear to God.
请别逼我开枪
Don't make me shoot you, please!
我对天发誓
I swear to God.
- Nick   - Nick 看后面
- Nick!   - Nick, behind you!
啊
Ah!
冷静
Easy!
Nick 拜托
Nick, please.
你还好吗
You okay?
不好 好疼啊
No, that hurt.
但是总比你们好些
But I gotta feel better than you guys.
有用吗
Is it working?
我想是的
I think so.
以防万一 我们应该再给他打一针
We should give him another shot just in case.
已经把解药都给他用上了
We gave him everything we had.
我们得把他弄回店里去
We just have to get him back to the shop.
那咱们快把他弄过去吧...走
Well, let's get him back there fast... let's go!
快点  我可不想解释
Let's hurry. Don't wanna explain
- 我们这是在干嘛   - 我也是
- what we're doing here.   - Me either.
- 他一直在发抖   - 希望他能撑到店里
- He's still shaking.   - I hope we're not too late.
- 他的脉搏很弱   - 他的身体特别冰凉
- His pulse is really slow.   - He's really cold to the touch.
伙计们 他的脉象在减弱
Guys, his pulse is slowing down,
- 而且快摸不到了   - 他快死了吗
- and it's getting weaker.   - Are we losing him?
也许我们应该使他保持体温
Maybe we should try to keep him warm.
我们应该给他盖个外套
We should put a coat on him.
Nick 能听到我说话吗
Nick, can you hear me?
Nick
Nick...
趁现在还不晚
Before it's too late.
你哥应该对此事负责 对吗
Your brother is responsible for this, right?
- 是的   - 他们没在
- Yeah.   - And they didn't find
- 飞机上找到他的尸体   - 没有
- his body on the plane?   - No.
好吧 我不知道你们是怎么处理家庭事务的
Well, I don't know how you guys handle family issues,
但是我希望你们不要让他逃脱惩罚
but I hope you're not gonna let him get away with this.
嘿 会没事的
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
你会好起来的
You're gonna be okay.
我喘不过气来了
I can't breathe.
你必须适应死亡的味道 尸体的气息
You must become accustomed to the smell of death.
你要我拿这些做什么
What do you want me to do with these?
把花塞进她身体里
Place the flowers in her.
然后缝起来
Then sew her shut.
这些花必须成为她的一部分
The flowers must become part of her
这样才能奏效
before they can be effective.
你等的时间越久
The longer you wait,
失去这个机会的风险就越大
the more you risk wasting the opportunity.
她只是暂时性死亡
This death does not last forever.
希望第二剂能有效果
I hope the second dose does it.
我们能做的也只有这样了
There's nothing more we can do.
我都不确定这么做是否有效
I'm not even sure this is going to work,
但是我也不知道还能...
but I just don't know what else...
该死
Damn it.
抱歉 我并不想这样
I'm sorry. I'm just trying not to.
我也是
Me too.
我得回局里去了
I gotta get back to the precinct,
处理下刚发生的事情
deal with what's happened.
我留下来
I'm staying.
也许你留下来最好
Probably best that you do.
如果那是我哥
If his brother was my brother...
那么
Well...
我大概就不该再回那儿了
I probably shouldn't go there.
是吗 你应该去
Oh, yeah, you should go there.
我会和你一起去
I'd go there with you.
哇哦 有情况
Whoa! Something's happening.
是好事 对吗
That's a good thing, right?
我想是的  我去拿些温水来
I think so. Let me get some warm water.
哦 喔
Oh! Whoo!
哦 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no! No, no, no, no!
别这样 别再变回去啊
Don't... don't do that. Let's not revert.
不 不 不  额 或许我们应该...
No, no, no! Uh, maybe we should...
- 我没想问 但是   - 你知道吗 还是把他铐起来吧
- I wasn't gonna ask, but...   - You know what, just do it.
因为我觉得被打一次已经够了
'Cause I think getting hit once was enough.
好了
Got him.
缝的可以了
That's enough.
用牙咬断线 然后打个结
Cut the thread with your teeth and tie it off.
快做啊
Do it!
比我想象中 见效还要快
It's working faster than I thought.
我觉得她喜欢你
I think she likes you.
搞定 网上已有新闻 链接已发送
刚过今晚8点 Eric Renard
Just after 8:00 P.M. this evening in Vienna, Austria,
Kronenberg家族的皇储 在离开奥地利
Eric Renard, crown prince of the Kronenberg family,
维也纳国际机场的途中
was killed when his car exploded
死于车辆爆炸
en route from the Vienna international airport.
目前还没有人宣告
No one has yet claimed responsibility
对这场悲剧负责
for this tragic event.
整个维也纳沈浸在哀痛中
All of Vienna is in mourning.
整个波特兰却没有
All of Portland isn't.
我是说 如果皇室成员要抓住一个格林
I mean, if the royals are going to this extent
不惜把事情弄到这个地步
to try to get a Grimm...
- 可能会有点疼   - 特别疼
- This might hurt.   - A lot!
喔 真是没开玩笑
Ow! Not kidding.
不好意思 刀口有点深
Sorry. That cut's a little deep.
我刚刚才知道
I didn't know that until now.
好吧 等下
All right, wait...
好了 来吧
Okay, let me have it.
我也在想这事
That's what I'm thinking.
如果他们这样不惜一切来抓Nick
If they're willing to do what they did,
那这其中一定有什么重要原因
there's got to be some serious stuff in the works.
Nick 能听到我说话吗
Nick, can you hear me?
嘿 他醒了
Hey, he's waking up.
Nick
Nick!
能听到我们说话吗
Can you hear us?
发生什么事情了
What's going on?
你这是在干嘛
What are you doing?
呃
Um...
检查下你的脉搏
Checking your pulse.
为什么
Why?
这有点...
That's got kind of a...
说来话长了
Long answer attached to it.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
- 为啥我被铐起来了   - 我们...
- Why am I handcuffed?   - We, um...
我们不想让你从床上掉下来
We didn't want you to fall over.
好...吧
O... Kay.
头好疼啊
That is a bad headache.
我是怎么到这儿来的
How'd I get here?
我们...把你带过来的
We... Brought you.
真疼啊
I'm really sore.
全身上下都疼
Kind of everywhere.
但是你气色好多了
But you look a lot better.
好太多了
A lot better.
这还是保守的说呢
Understatement.
你们发生什么意外了么
Were you all in an accident?
算是吧
Of a sort.
你什么都不记得了吗
You don't remember anything?
你拆了石膏
You got your cast off.
- 是的   - 你记得这个
- Yeah, I did.   - You remember that.
我记得你说你要去
I remember you saying you were going to.
你记得的最后一件事是什么
What's the last thing you remember?
呃 我不太确定
Uh, I'm not really sure.
我们当时在一个码头
We were at the shipping yard.
对 我记得这个
Yeah, I remember that.
我们试图阻止事态的发展
We were trying to stop what was happening...
然后你拿着解药
And you had the medicine.
但是我们分散了 我在追着谁
But we got separated, and I was chasing somebody.
- Baron   - Samedi
- Baron...   - Samedi.
戴帽子的那个人
The guy with the hat.
帽子伙计 你想起来了
The hat dude. You got it.
我当时在追他
I was chasing him.
然后我们摔倒了
And then we fell.
我发现了有我照片的护照
And I found a passport with my photo.
但却是别人的名字 Thomas什么的
But somebody else's name... Thomas something.
差不多就是这样
And that's pretty much it.
我肯定是被袭击了
I must've gotten hit.
我猜你们找到了我 然后把我带到了这里 对吗
And I guess you guys found me and brought me here, right?
或者不是这样的
Or maybe not.
我漏掉什么了吗
Am I leaving something out?
- 对不起   - 别 别 别 别
- Sorry.   - No, no, no, no.
你说吧
You go.
我觉得还是Juliette说吧
I think Juliette should go.
好吧
O... Kay.
我把事情搞砸了 是吗
I blew it, didn't I?
我把事情搞砸了 他们跑了 是吗
I screwed it up and they got away?
不是 Nick 事情比这还复杂的多
No, Nick, there's much more to it than that.
那就告诉我啊
So just tell me.
他...制服了你
He... got you.
就像他制服了其他人一样 你看
Like he got the others. See?
你在哀悼吗
简直肝肠寸断
我对此深表同情
我要确认
你是否去度假了
是的 我一下班就走了
但是我想事情会变得非常有趣的 不是吗
我也这么想
你的大家庭如何了
我们分开度假
很好 这样最好
记得寄给我明信片
圣乔治医院打来的电话
You got a call from St. Joe's.
昨晚在那个酒吧打群架的
One of the guys that was involved
一个家伙挂掉了
in that bar fight last night just died.
恐怕这已经变成一起凶杀案了
So I'm afraid we've got ourselves a murder.
犯罪报告里列出了一个叫Thomas Schirach的人
Crime report lists a Thomas Schirach
有可能是嫌疑犯
as being identified as the probable.
这就说得通了 他...
That would make sense. He, uh...
他被指认也是那场因毒素感染而引发暴乱的始作俑者
He was identified as a possible source of the outbreak.
我们正在做背景调查
Uh, we're doing a background now.
发了全境通告 但是
Put out an apb, but...
除了目击证人的外貌描述外
We don't have much more than a description
没有其他信息
based on witness reports.
我们也查了酒吧是否有监控录像
Checked to see if there was surveillance at the bar,
但是看起来有人破坏了系统
but it looks like somebody destroyed the system...
并拿走了录像
And took the file.
- 这案子谁负责   - Holtby和Bauer
- Who's on it?   - Holtby and Bauer.
很好
Good.
很好 我稍后会跟他们确认
Good. I'll check with them later.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
至少没人受伤
At least nobody got really hurt.
我是说 没有 重伤
I mean, really hurt...Badly.
你吓到了一些人
You scared a few people.
哦 没错 你绝对吓到人了
Oh, yeah, you definitely did that.
你看起来不像知道自己在做什么 Nick
Well, it's not like you knew what you were doing, Nick.
你甚至都不记得了
You don't even remember.
被感染了可不是什么好的借口
Being under the influence isn't a very good defense.
但是你受的感染
Under the influence
可不是一般的感染
of what you were under the influence of...
- 这就不一样了   - 我们要怎么解释啊
- that's different.   - How are we gonna explain it?
其实你不用解释 看看我们挂的彩
You don't have to. We sort of had it
大家就都懂了
explained to us in a very physical way,
我估计你不想弄得
which I don't think you really wanna share
人人皆知
with anybody else.
我非常抱歉
I'm really sorry.
Nick 你当时不知道
Nick, you didn't know.
听着 今晚你经历太多事情了
Look, I think that after everything
你需要好好睡一觉
you've gone through tonight you need a lotta sleep.
所以 你现在应该跟我回家 去睡觉
So... You should come home with me now and get it.
完全同意
Agreed.
是的 你真的要好好休息
Yeah, you really need some downtime.
我觉得我们都应该好好休息一下
I think we all could use a little downtime.
感谢上帝一切结束了
Thank God it's over.
我只是很欣慰我没有杀人
I'm just glad I didn't kill anybody.
我给你泡点茶
I'm gonna go make you some tea.
你怎么不先上楼躺着
Why don't you go upstairs and get in bed?
额 我不想一个人上去躺
Well, I'd rather not do that alone.
你知道 我很开心你好多了
You know, I am glad that you're feeling better,
但是不行
but no.
你得乖乖上楼睡觉去
You're gonna go upstairs and go to sleep,
等你睡着后我就
and I'm going to pace at the end of the bed
去床上
until you do.
我觉得你说得对
You know, I think you're right.
混乱的一晚 哈
Hell of a night, huh?
很高兴我们都挺过来了
Glad to see we all survived.
嘿 Nick在哪 我一晚上都没看到他
Hey, where's Nick? I didn't see him all night.
哦 他当时在啊
Oh, he was there.
他去对付最糟糕的那部分了
He got the worst of some of it.
现在正在休息调养
He's taking some r&r.
只挂了一个真是不可思议
Amazing there was only one fatality.
啥
What?
昨晚打群架的一个家伙
Guy in a bar fight.
谁负责这案子
Who's working it?
Holtby和Bauer
Holtby and Bauer.
嘿 你觉得
Hey, what do you...
好吧 我猜我说完了
Okay, then. Guess I'm done here.
昨晚Nick引起的那场群架有人死了
Somebody died in the bar fight Nick was in?
我还不清楚死亡原因及细节
I don't know the details or what the cause of death was.
我可是非常清楚
Well, I have a pretty good idea
死亡的原因
what the cause of death was.
我们要怎么处理这件事
How we gonna deal with this?
要非常小心
Very carefully.
有警察看到我在酒吧里 和Rosalee还有Juliette在一起
Uniform saw me at the bar, along with Rosalee and Juliette.
我和她们都会接受询问
I'll be questioned and so will they.
你准备怎么跟他们说
What are you gonna tell them?
不管我们怎么说 都必须说法一致
Whatever we tell them, it has to be the same story.
现在
Now right now,
他们以为要找的人是Thomas Schirach
they think they're looking for Thomas Schirach,
我们要确保他们一直这么想
and we need to make sure that they keep thinking that way.
因为这是我们保护Nick的唯一方式
'Cause that is the only way we can protect Nick.
Hank 一切还好吗
Hank. Everything okay?
- Nick怎么样了   - 他在睡觉
- How's Nick?   - He's asleep.
看起来似乎一切正常
Everything seems to be normal.
我们有点小麻烦
Well, we've got a complication.
你能来香料店一趟吗
Can you meet us at the spice shop?
好的 要我叫他起来吗
Yeah, should I wake him up?
不 让他睡吧
No, let him sleep.
好的
Okay.
但这不是他的错
But it wasn't his fault!
我是说 你也看到他的样子了 他想要杀了我们
I mean, you saw him. He was trying to kill us.
当然不是特指我们...
I mean, not us personally...
- 只是泛指   - 这不是什么有力的辩解
- Generally speaking.   - Not a great defense.
你知道你这是 叫我们干什么吧
You know what you're asking us to do?
我什么都干过
Nothing I haven't already done.
嘿
Hey!
Hey.
出什么事了
What's the problem?
有个和Nick在酒吧打斗的人死了
One of the men that Nick fought at the bar has died.
哦 不
Oh, no.
- 他当时已经不是自己了   - 没用的
- He wasn't himself.   - It doesn't matter.
你都没法解释清楚的事情 怎么去辩护
You can't defend what you can't explain.
所以Nick现在是杀人犯了
So Nick is a murderer.
- 严格意义上讲是这样的   - 但是
- Technically.   - But...
目前为止 没人知道Nick那晚在酒吧
So far, no one knows Nick was in the bar.
那个被认定为嫌疑犯的人
The man responsible for the death
叫Thomas Schirach
has been identified as Thomas Schirach.
我觉得这挺好的 因为我不认为
Which works for me, because I don't think
那是Nick的错
we can blame Nick for what happened...
他当时中毒了 他有可能会死
he was poisoned. He would've died.
只要他们继续寻找Thomas Schirach
As long as they're looking for Thomas Schirach,
Nick就是清白的
Nick is in the clear.
多讽刺啊 我哥为了把Nick运出美国
Ironically, the false identity my brother created
制造的假身份现在帮了我们大忙
to get Nick out of the country is working in our favor.
如果他们在监控记录里看到了Nick怎么办
What if they see Nick in the surveillance recordings?
目前为止 没人找到录像
So far, none has been found.
好的
Okay.
指定了两名探员管理这件案子
Two Detectives have been assigned to the case.
他们会从警方报告上看到
From the police reports, they're gonna know
那晚我和两个女人一起
that there were two women with me that night,
他们会询问我们三个
and they're gonna wanna talk to all of us.
我知道我们该怎么说
I know what we should tell them.
肯定不会是真相
And it is definitely not the truth.
没错
Right.
Hank 你赞成这样做吗
Hank, are you good with this?
Nick因为自己都不知道自己在干嘛
I'm not good with Nick going to prison
就被关进监狱 我可不同意
for something he didn't even know he was doing.
你们也听到了
You heard him.
他什么都不记得了
He doesn't remember anything.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
所以我们为了保护Nick 要集体撒谎
So we are all going to lie to protect Nick.
如果他发现了怎么办
What happens if he finds out?
希望他能给我们办个小派对
Hopefully he throws us a little party.
他不会发现的
He's not going to find out.
至少 暂时不会
At least, not for a little while.
听着 有三件事 我们要达成一致
Now look, we all have to agree on three things.
我们在追踪受感染的疑犯
We were chasing down infected suspects,
其中一名是Thomas Schirach
one of them was identified as Thomas Schirach,
你俩当时在场
and you two were there
是因为你们手里有能治愈此症状的解药
because you had a treatment that was effective.
看吧 还不错吧
See? Not so bad.
有一部分是真的
Some of it's true.
现在我们要商定一下细节
Now we have to decide on the details.
不然会漏出马脚 功亏一篑
Because that is how you get caught.
嗯
Hmm.
什么时候的事
What time was that?
嗯
Uh-huh.
他有同伙吗
Anybody else with him?
嘿
Hey.
听说你们在处理酒吧斗殴杀人事件
Heard you guys got the bar fight kill.
恩啊 棘手的案子啊
Yeah. Hell of a case.
所有的目击证人都说那个叫Thomas Schirach的人
All the witnesses say this Thomas Schirach guy
是个彻头彻尾的魔头
was a freaking monster.
高大 凶残
Big, bad.
他们怎么都无法阻止他
There was nothingthey could do to stop him.
在酒吧和人斗殴后
After the bar fight,
很明显又闯进附近的人家 起了冲突
apparently he accosted some family in their house.
这样啊
Really?
谢谢
Thanks.
猜我发现了啥
Guess what I found out.
被袭击的那家
That family that was attacked in that house...
Avery先生...
Mr. Avery...
说有几个人在警察来之前 就到了他们家
claims some guys showed up before the unis got there.
声称自己是警察 告诉他们进屋去
Said they were cops. Told them to go back inside.
他说Schirach逃走了
He says Schirach got away
因为等警察到的时候 他们都不见了
because when the unis got there, they were all gone.
酒吧有监控录像么
They have surveillance at the bar?
之前有的 打架的时候给弄坏了
There was at the time. It was trashed in the fight.
所有录像都不见了
All the files were missing.
可能他很聪明 都拿走了
Maybe he was smart enough to take it.
他没拿任何东西
He didn't take anything else.
他只是来找事儿的
He was just looking for trouble.
好吧 如果有啥需要帮忙的
Well, if there's anything I can help you with,
- 跟我说一声   - 你可以在这边帮我们
- let me know.   - You can stay here and fill out
- 填这些报告   - 拜拜
- all these reports for us.   - Bye.
进来
Yeah?
刚跟Holtby和Bauer
Just talked to Holtby
- 小聊了下   - 嗯
- and Bauer.   - Mmhmm.
酒吧的监控系统被毁了
Surveillance system at the bar got trashed.
然后呢
That so?
这个挺好的
That was convenient.
你认为是怎么回事
What do you think happened?
我想应该有人拿走了闪存盘
I think somebody took the flash drive,
把办公室弄得像群架后的
trashed the office to make it looked like
战场一样
it happened in the fight.
- 这对我们有利啊   - 是的
- That's lucky for us.   - Yeah.
只要没人发现就好
As long as it doesn't turn up.
- 有时间吗   - 嗯
- Got a minute?   - Yeah.
长官 不好意思打扰了 就问几个问题
Sorry to bother you, sir.Just a couple questions.
报告上说你昨晚在那个酒吧里
Report says you were at the bar last night.
是的
That's right.
有两个女人跟你一起
There were two women with you.
报告上没有他们名字
The report doesn't give their names.
我们需要调查下
We need to follow up.
我写下来给你们
I'll write them down for you.
Nick
Nick?
嘿 你怎么了 身上这么冷
Hey, what's wrong? You feel cold.
嘿 醒醒
Hey, wake up!
Nick Nick
Nick! Nick!
Nick
Nick!
几点了
What time is it?
911 什么情况
911.What is your emergency?
你在给谁打电话
Who are you calling?
怎么了
What's wrong?
什么紧急状况
What is your emergency?
没事 误打了 不好意思
Nothing. I made a mistake, I'm sorry.
额...
Wha...
你感觉怎么样
how do you feel?
感觉好像...不知道 还好啦
Like... I don't know. Fine.
除了我的脸有点疼
Except my face hurts a little bit.
你得去看医生
You need to see a doctor.
为啥
Why?
你给我号脉干嘛 我感觉挺好哒
What are you doing that for? I feel fine.
你刚才看起来可不好
You didn't look fine.
好吧 那我刚才看起来怎么样
Well, how did I look?
你看着像是死了
You looked dead.
你体温真的很低
And you were really cold to the touch,
我测不到你的脉搏 现在仍跳得很慢
and I couldn't find your pulse, and it's still really slow.
你确定你感觉还好
Are you sure you feel okay?
在你说我像个死人之前 感觉还好
Well, I did until you told me I was dead.
我是认真的 你得去看医生
I'm serious. You're seeing a doctor.
看兽医算不
Does a vet count?
Nick
Nick.
我只是...想让我心跳加快点
I'm just...Trying to get my heart rate up.
你真的吓到我了
You really scared me.
嘿
Hey.
对不起让你担心了 但是我真觉得身体还好
I'm sorry, but I really do feel okay.
我觉得你应该躺下来
I think you need to just lie back down
我们一步步慢慢来
and we'll take this a little bit more slowly.
这个可以有
I can do that.
嘿
Hey.
我真的没问题
I'm really okay.
是时候了
It's time.
干嘛
For what?
收获你的成果
To reap what you have sewn.
- 你会想填满它的   - 用啥填满
- You'll want to fill that up.   - With what?
这个对皮肤很好哦
It's really very good for the skin...
对你小孩也好
And for your child.
额...
Mmm...
看来那群巫毒僵尸
Looks like our voodoo hordes
用光了我们所有的菖蒲(一种草本植物)
used up all our acorus calamus
和古柯属植物(用来提炼可卡因)
and the erythroxylum novogranatense.
以防万一 我会再订些货
I'll order some more just in case.
你知道那玩意是多久前的么
Do you know how old that stuff was anyway?
我爹在的时候买的哦
I think my dad ordered it.
还好它没有变质 因为你知道
Good thing it didn't go bad,cause, you know...
僵尸祸害每一代人 差不多都要用到很多这种药
One zombie romp every generation or so was plenty.
你好
Hello.
要买什么吗
Can I help you?
- 你是Rosalee Calvert吗   - 是的
- Rosalee Calvert?   - Yes.
我是 Bauer探员 这位是Holtby探员
I'm Detective Bauer. This is Detective Holtby.
我们有几个问题想问你
We'd like to ask you a few questions
是关于前几天在酒吧里发生的事故
about what happened the other night at the bar.
我们了解到你当时在场
We understand you were there.
是的 我在场 请进
Yes, I was.Please come in.
你是和Sean Renard队长一起去的 是吧
You were there with police Captain Sean Renard.
是的
Yes.
Calvert 女士 你是做什么的
What is it that you do, Ms. Calvert?
我是一名药剂师
I'm an apothecary.
我们为多种健康问题 提供一些草药和
We offer herbal and organic treatments and remedies
有机治疗和救治
for a variety of health issues.
这就是我那天和队长在一起的原因
That's why I was with the Captain.
我们试图医治
We were attempting to treat
由一种感染性很强的神经毒素引发的暴动
an apparent outbreak of a highly infectious neurotoxin
那种毒素会导致拉撒路综合症
that causes Lazarus syndrome.
我对这个病的治疗方法比较熟悉
I was familiar with the treatment,
跟我一起的那个女人也是
as was this woman who was with me.
那个人是Juliette Silverton
That would be Juliette Silverton?
是的
Yes.
你们有听过一个叫Thomas Schirach的人吗
Have you ever heard of a Thomas Schirach?
是的 有人说
Yes, I was told
他可能是制造这个并发症的始作俑者
he's the possible source of the outbreak
也是在酒吧里打群架的
and the man responsible for the fight
主谋
that happened at the bar.
能描述下他吗
Could you describe him?
不好意思 我从没见过他
No, I'm sorry. I never saw him.
嘿
Hey.
两个警探刚来过
Two Detectives were just here at the shop.
他们大概15分钟前走的
They left about 15 minutes ago.
我确保他们不会再回来 才打给你
I waited to make sure they weren't coming back.
情况如何
How did it go?
按计划编的那故事
I stuck to the story.
- 他们相信吗   - 我觉得信了
- They believe you? - I think so.
我去开门
Got it!
我这会没法多说了
Um, I can't really talk right now.
Nick醒了
Nick's awake.
你们来这儿干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
额 我们来找Juliette Silverton
Uh, we're looking for Juliette Silverton.
哦 你女朋友啊
Oh, it's your girlfriend.
我们没想到你俩在一起
We didn't, uh, put two and two together.
Juliette在家吗
Is Juliette home?
有什么事吗
Is there a problem?
她没事 队长告诉我们她名字的
Not for her. The Captain gave us her name.
她可能目睹了酒吧的一场斗殴
As a possible witness to a bar fight.
你们要找她问酒吧斗殴的事
You wanna talk to her about a bar fight?
嗯 是啊 有个人因为这事死了
Yeah, well, one of the guys in the fight died.
就几个问题 很快就好
It's just a couple of questions. It won't take very long.
他什么时候死的
When did he die?
打完架 在医院里
In the hospital, after the fight.
可能受伤太严重了
I guess he was beat up pretty bad.
总之现在这是凶杀案了 我们接下了
Anyway, now it's murder and we got it.
不过 总比你接的那些神精病案子强
But it's better than those crazies you were dealing with.
嗯 进来吧
Well, come on in.
我会配合你们回答问题的
I will answer whatever questions you guys have.
你和Sean Renard队长在一起
You were there with police Captain Sean Renard?
是的
Yes.
你听说过一个叫Thomas Schirach的人吗
You ever hear of a Thomas Schirach?
是的 他们说他是这次
Yeah, I believe he was the one they said
斗殴事件的主谋
was responsible for the bar fight.
那你在那干什么
And what were you doing there?
我们在
We were...
试图帮助控制这起
Attempting to help the situation
毒素感染突发事件
with the outbreak.
和我在一起的Rosalee Calvert
The woman I was with, Rosalee Calvert, and I,
我们比较熟悉这种
were familiar with the treatment
罕见的神经毒素的治疗方式
for this rare neurotoxin.
传染性很强 会引起拉撒路综合症
It's highly infectious and causes Lazarus syndrome.
你见过嫌疑人吗
You ever get a look at the suspect?
没有
No.
没有 我们赶到的时候 他已经走了
No, he was gone by the time we got there.
Nick 你还好吗
Nick, you okay?
没事 就是打碎了个杯子
Yeah. Just broke a coffee cup.
我们问完了
We're done here.
Burkhardt 小心那个咖啡哦
Be careful with that coffee, Burkhardt.
它也许被加了料
It might be loaded.
小心别烫到
Wouldn't want you to get burned.
- 谢谢你们   - 谢谢
- Thanks, guys.   - Thank you.
有人因为酒吧的事情死了
Someone died in that bar fight?
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
你根本不知道自己在干嘛
You didn't know what you were doing.
- 那不是真正的你   - 这不重要
- You weren't yourself.   - That doesn't matter.
如果我杀人了 我就得去自首
If I killed somebody, I have to turn myself in.
我们同意一起编个故事
We all agreed on a story.
- 都有谁   - 我 Monroe Rosalee
- Who agreed?   - Me, Monroe, Rosalee,
- Hank 还有你的队长   - 所以你们都在撒谎
- Hank, your Captain.   - So you're all lying?
是为了保护你
To protect you.
你们不能这么做
You can't do that.
我杀人了
I killed someone.
Nick 你现在去自首的话
Nick, if you turn yourself in,
我们就都有麻烦了
we're all in trouble.
Nick
Nick!
- 你不能这么做   - 别管这事 Hank
- You can't do this.   - Get out of my way, Hank.
我已经掺和进来了 其他人也是
I'm already in the way, and so are the rest of us.
我们决定了 你当时精神状态不好
We made a decision. You were not in good shape.
完全不知道自己在做什么
You had no idea what you were doing.
我已经听过这些了 Hank
I've heard it all, Hank.
Nick 你当时想杀我
You tried to kill me, Nick.
你也想杀了Monroe和队长
You tried to kill Monroe and the Captain.
如果不是我们合起来 制服你
And you would have had we not worked together
你已经杀了我们
to take you down.
问问Juliette被你打后 感觉如何
And ask Juliette how it felt to get hit by you.
如果你现在还想自首 去吧
Now, you wanna turn yourself in, go ahead.
但是 这次就是你一个人了
But you're going to do it alone.
- 喂   - Sean么
- Yeah?   - Sean?
还好么
Ca va?
- 母亲  - 你怎么样
- Mother.  - How are you?
抱歉 我没认出这个号码
I'm sorry, I didn't recognize the number.
你也不该认得
You are not supposed to.
我听说了 你哥哥在维也纳的事情了
I heard what happened to your half-brother in Vienna.
嗯 很悲剧
Yes. Tragic.
也很活该
And well deserved.
谢谢你 我们再联系
Thank you. Let's talk soon.
我听说你打算投案自首
I hear you wanna do the right thing.
你也要劝我别这样
You're gonna try to talk me out of it.
我给你看个东西
Let me show you something.
认得出你自己吗
Recognize yourself?
注意那个拿刀的人
Pay close attention to the guy with the knife.
他叫Mitchell Zinc
His name was Mitchell Zinc.
凌晨5点40分死于医院
He died in the hospital at 5:40 in the morning.
如果你没有打倒他
And if you hadn't done what you did,
你可能已经死了
you probably be dead.
Nick 有些时候就是这样
This is one of those times, Nick,
你游走在两个完全不同的世界里
where you walk in two worlds.
你知道你为什么要这么做 但是你不能说出去
You know why you did it. You just can't explain it,
至少不能在法庭上说
at least not in a court of law.
有时候正义并不那么明显
Sometimes justice isn't obvious.
有些事情你必须要清楚 Nick
You have to understand something, Nick.
是我哥哥对你做的这些事
My brother did this to you.
这是毁掉一个格林的计划
It was all part of a plan to destroy a Grimm,
或者至少强迫格林为他效力
or at least to get one to work for him.
如果你去自首了
And if you turn yourself in...
那你就完全顺从了他们的意愿
You will give them exactly what they want.
Burkhardt
Burkhardt.
还好吗
How's it going?
挺好的
Okay.